# SID CARROLL - FULLSTACK DESIGNER

- sidcarroll.works
- sidcarrollworks@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/sidcarrollworks

#### SUMMARY

UX/UI Designer with full stack development experience and 4 years of graphic design experience. Adept at creating powerful, user-friendly interfaces with purposeful design. Background in graphic design paired with dev experience allows for rapid prototyping at no cost to functionality or useability. Specializes in clear, clean, and informed design.

### **EXPERIENCE**



### Frontend Engineer / UX/UI Designer

Botpress

Mar 2022 - June 2022 (4 months)

Worked on a team of 4 tasked with redesigning the Botpress studio.

Redesigning the UI to be easy to use but powerful pro tool.

Implemented a color coding system to give users valuable information about their conversation flow at a glance.

Designed multiple custom icons to save space and reduce text.

Rapidly prototyped features and user flows.

#### kabloom!

### Frontend Engineer / UX/UI Designer

Kabloom Team Building Aug 2021 - Mar 2022 (8 months)

With a team of 2 architected an event booking system that integrated with Stripe and Hubspot that generated an average of ~\$3200 in revenue per month.

Planned multiple product pages that decreased the bounce rate from 70% bounce rate to 45%.

Designed multiple graphics to be used around the website as well as an SVG animation.



#### **Head Graphic Designer / Typesetter**

Sheridan Printing

Jul 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 2 months)

Designed and printed all types of print media, logos, envelopes...

Worked with a team of two printers to reduce job time by 15%.

Maintained and operated 2 digital printers that reduced job costs by 20%.

Put together a collection of retail items that brought in ~\$1500 a month.

Automated large, reoccuring jobs that led to an 25% decrease in print time.



#### **Junior Software Engineer**

Instrumental Systems
Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Designed a program that interfaced with an engine control unit.

Programmed a prototype application that laid the ground work for the app using Electron.

PCB solder work and board testing for Amazon warehouse lightbars.

#### SHERIDAN PRINTING

## **Junior Graphic Designer**

Bighorn Design

Apr 2017 - Sep 2017 (6 months)

Feb 2019 - Nov 2019 (10 months)

Learned how to effectively communicate with clients and customers.

Gained lots of experience designing tshirts, logos, business cards and more.

Maintained the customer floor and worked with customers.

Handled walking design jobs.

## **EDUCATION**



## **Holberton School**

Computer Software Engineering 2017 - 2019

## **SKILLS**

HTML	UX/UI Design	React	Illustrator
CSS	Graphic Design	Vue	After Effects
Javascript	Brand Design	TailwindCSS	Photoshop
	SVG Animation	Figma	InDesign